Jackie Martin Papers
Jackie Martin Papers
- Negatives and contacts
  - Assorted negatives, 1935-1965
    - W.R. Hearst's 76th birthday party at Cissy Patterson's 15 Dupont Circle, Town and Country, 1940 (Box 40)
    - A.N.P.A. party for Cissy Patterson at Waldorf, NYC; banquet following (Box 40)
    - Dower House; Boss and Princess Alice, Tafts, etc., 29 May 1944 (Box 40)
    - Cal Carrington "E.P." (Box 40)
    - Tyson debut party (Box 40)
    - Democratic Convention, Chicago, 1940; Farley (Box 40)
    - Democratic Convention, 1940 (Box 40)
    - Assignments: Washington D.C. and New York after 1960
      - Guggenheim Plantation "Poco Sabo," South Carolina (Box 40)
      - Press Club trip to NYC, Lee Walsh Administration (Box 40)
      - Katherine Embrey; Mr. and Mrs. Bill Lee at Ghengis Kahn (Box 40)
      - Wedding of Mr. and Mrs. Alan Randall (Ann Hagen) in Westchester (Box 40)
      - Vaux Owen, President National Federation of Federal Employees, 04 May (Box 40)
      - Judge Eugene Worley, Court of Patent Appeals, 1961 (Box 40)
      - Nickey and Janine DeRachat party honoring, Aug 1962-Sep 1962 (Box 40)
      - Dr. Werner and Estelle Teufel Party, 2101 Conn, Dec 1962 (Box 40)
    - Mrs. Brown, mother of kidnapped girl (Box 40)
    - World's Fair, Chicago, 1939 (Box 40)
    - Democratic Convention, Philadelphia, 1936; Gov. and Mrs. Early's party (Box 40)
    - Tony and Mrs. Biddle; George Allen, District Democratic Committee (Box 40)
    - Party at Old Press Club, Friendship (Box 40)
    - McLean's christening (Box 40)
    - McLean's Easter Party Times-Herald and Town and Country, 1945 (Box 40)
    - Evalyn McLean and Fannie Brice (Box 40)
    - Mme. Zoltan Tildy, Hungary (Box 40)
    - Eve Currie and Mrs. Gilbert Grosvenor (Box 40)
    - Egyptian Reception for King's birthday, 11 Feb 1946 (Box 40)
    - Embassies (Box 41)
    - McCall's party; Mrs. Roosevelt, Carlton, 14 May 1949 (Box 41)
    - French hat party, Lancelot, 25 Feb 1949 (Box 41)
    - Copies and photos; FDR letters to Grace Tully (Box 41)
    - Hungarian Prime Minister at Congress before Red Coup (Box 41)
    - Cajigas, Fernandez, Vinsons, Snyders; J. Edgar Hoover and FBI (Box 41)
    - Fred M. Vinsons; M. Truman; circus; White House office (Box 41)
    - Polish National Women's Party (Box 41)
    - Maria Martins; Embassy and N.Y., Dec 1947 (Box 41)
    - Saudi Arabia Ambassador Asad (Box 41)
    - Irish Minister and wife (Box 41)
    - Awards at Belgium Embassy, 18 Mar 1948; 06 May 1948 (Box 41)
    - Mme. Wei luncheon at Embassy, 10 Feb 1946 (Box 41)
    - Cuban Embassy President Prio, 10 Dec 1948; 19 Apr 1948 (Box 41)
    - President Alleman's arrival (Box 41)
    - Maude Adam's in Hollywood (Box 41)
    - Post Office Dept (Box 41)
    - White House cars (Box 41)
    - Felicia and Ellen, Dower House; party for Felicia's book, NYC (Box 41)
    - Olga Kahler, Lantana, Florida; Felicia Gizycka, contacts (Box 41)
    - Treasury (Box 41)
    - Interior (Box 41)
    - Inside Capitol; new and old House of Rep.
      - 5 Congresswomen "running for election" (Box 41)
      - 6 Congresswomen at Mayflower, 1947 (Box 41)
      - Pageboy cheering, Senator Brewater, Sec. Leo Allen, Karl Stefan, Senator Vandenberg, Spator Martin (Box 41)
    - Mexican Embassy party, June 9, 1946 (Box 41)
    - Brazilian Reception, President Dutra, 20 May 1949 (Box 41)
    - Airshots of Washington (Box 41)
    - Washington from top of Capitol (Box 41)
    - City of Washington from top of Monument (Box 41)
    - Department of Agriculture; Sec. and Mrs. Brannan (Box 41)
    - Commerce Dept: Weather Bureau, Patent Office, Coast and Geodetic Survey (Box 41)
    - Bureau of Standards, Sec. Sawyer in office (Box 41)
    - Labor (Box 41)
    - Alicia Patterson Guggenheim, adopted French children (Box 41)
    - "Ex-Sevice Men Can Expect This" McCall's, 19 Oct 1943 (Box 41)
    - "Glamour Pony of the Youngest Set" N.Y. Mirror, 28 Sep 1947 (Box 41)
    - GI and baby at American University (Box 41)
    - Sisters of USSH Hospital, 06 Jun 1948 (Box 41)
    - Sol Bloom's birthday party (Box 41)
    - President Eisenhower: Eagle War Dept, 21 Oct 1947 (Box 41)
    - Justice Vinson's swearing-in Pathfinder, 24 Jun 1946 (Box 41)
    - Walter Reed Hospital and Martin Bomber (Box 41)
    - Dogs of War, Mar 1944; Country Gentleman (Box 41)
    - WASPs, Camp Davis (Box 41)
    - Kenmore, Monroe office (Box 41)
    - Oveta Culp Hobby: New WAAC Chief, 1942 (Box 41)
    - Oveta Culp Hobby (Box 41)
    - Margaret Truman concert, 22 Dec 1947 (Box 41)
    - King George VI and Queen in U.S. with Roosevelts, 1939 (Box 41)
    - Truman, Grandma Moses, Mrs. Teddy and Mrs. Eleanor Roosevelt; Press Club Awards, 14 May 1949 (Box 41)
    - Roosevelt signs Declaration of War, 08 Dec 1941 (Box 41)
    - Duke and Duchess of Windsor at Willard Hotel (Box 41)
    - NAT signing, 04 Apr 1949 (Box 41)
    - Margaret Truman and "NET" (Box 41)
    - A.N.W.C. lunch for Mrs. Truman at Statler, 07 Dec 1948 (Box 41)
    - President Truman at Congress, Jan 1948 (Box 41)
    - Clare Boothe Luce; office; Congress; NYC with husband; girl's school at Capitol; contacts of negatives that INP kept (Box 41)
    - Convention (Box 41)
    - Bernard Baruch (Box 41)
    - Winston Churchill, Ottawa; White House, 1942 (Box 41)
    - Pool shot - Churchill in Ottawa (Box 41)
    - President Truman decorates the 442nd (Box 41)
    - Cissy and Joe Patterson (Box 41)
    - GOP Convention in Philadelphia, 1940; Stasser masterminds Wilkies' nomination (Box 41)
    - William Randolph Hearst's Christmas party at San Simeon, copies, originals were contax (Box 41)
    - "The President's Desk", 18 Apr 1949; Truman (Box 41)
    - Copies for Leila Morse; Library of Congress (Box 41)
    - Miscellaneous contacts (Box 41)
    - Arlington National Cemetary, used for Times-Herald full-page layout (Box 41)
    - McNamara's shot (Box 41)
    - Landscape scenery, possibly Winona School (Box 41)
    - Normandy sculpture (Box 41)
    - Luftwaife story, contacts only (Box 41)
  - Europe negatives, 1951-1954
    - Pictures made at "front" 7 years later on trip with Charlotte Drummond (Box 42)
    - Bruyeres, the Vosges; also same spot where I photographed the booby-trapped [German] in 1944 Fountain at Salon, France; Aug 1951 (Box 42)
    - Luxuiel, France, 1951 (Box 42)
    - Nancy, France (Box 42)
    - Golbey (Epinal), France, 1951 (Box 42)
    - Vesoul, France, 1951 (Box 42)
    - The American Cemetary, Epinal, 1951; between Epainal and Arches (Box 42)
    - Belmont, the Vosges, 1951 (Box 42)
    - Memorial to the 36th at St. Raphael, France, Aug 1953 (Box 42)
    - The fountain at Barjols, Aug 1953 (Box 42)
    - Route between N-7-Crest - Die, 16 Aug 1954 (Box 42)
    - Top of Mt. Etna and Rome Airport, 1953; Alps near Zurich (Box 42)
    - Anzio, Beach-head - air, 1953 (Box 42)
    - Longue-Sur-Mer receives the Croix de Guerre I and II (Box 42)
    - French Senator, Louis Andre; Meuvaines, Calvados; Helen Kirkpatrick (Box 42)
    - Lichtenstein and Rhein Falls (Box 42)
    - Sustin Pass (Box 42)
    - Montreux, Switzerland (Box 42)
    - St. Tropez, 10th Anniversary of the invasion of southern France, 15 Aug 1954 (Box 42)
    - Strasbourg, on way back from Montreux (Box 42)
    - Strasbourg summer vacation; Jul 1951-Aug 1951; Alice Rogers Hager to Montreux in Minx (Box 42)
    - Between Colmar and Strasbourg; the other side of the Vosges, 1944; made in 1954 (Box 42)
    - Dr. Truvey at Plan de la Tour; Aug 1953; back from visit at San Remo with Clare and Henry Luce (Box 42)
    - East of St. Raphael; French Naval assault spot August 14, 1944, Aug 1953 (Box 42)
  - Europe, 1932-1949
    - Copenhagen, trip with Ruth Bryan Owens, 1932; 40 4x5 (Box 42)
    - S.S. Champlain going over; return from Plymouth, 1932 (Box 42)
    - England, 1932 (Box 42)
    - St. Ives, 1932 (Box 42)
    - France; Paris and Versailles, 1932; 22 4x5 (Box 42)
    - Vikingland tour, 20 Nov 1949
      - Bastogne, Reims, Brussels (Box 42)
      - Denmark and Norway; Oslo, charges party; Travel Bureau party; Viking ship (Box 42)
      - Ireland and Iceland; president's reception (Box 42)
      - Sweden and Finland; Stockholm, Bertil; Helsinki; Ambassador's Party; N.K. Stockholm; Foreign Office party; Estelle Manville Bernadette (Box 42)
      - Royal Cup China; Copenhagen; Foreign Office Party; Cadain Hotel (Box 42)
    - Color transparencies (binder), Paris; various people, street scenes, "Cylindre" story, Paul Huf models (Box 42)
  - Newspaper negatives, 1939-1948; rollies and 4x5, more than 200 total
    - Fredericksburg Dog Mart, Times-Herald, 14 Oct 1939 (Box 42)
    - Wife of General Clay packs for Germany, Times-Herald, 04 April 1946; 6 contacts + 6 negatives; additional contacts (Box 42)
    - Soviet Reception at Embassy: 28th Anniversary of Red Army and Navy (Novikov and wife greet Canadian General), Times-Herald, 23 Feb 1946; 5 contacts and 5 negatives (Box 42)
    - Lady Astor at Dunbar High School (with Sol Bloom; students), Times-Herald, 09 Apr 1946; 2 contacts and 2 negatives; additional contacts (Box 42)
    - Callie Shaw (Carolyn Hagner Shaw), social mentor, Times-Herald, 09 Apr 1946; Contacts for negatives 1-3; additional contacts (Box 42)
    - Chinese Cardinal and Senator McCarran at Chinese Embassy, Times-Herald, 09 Apr 1946; 1 contact and 1 negative; additional contacts (Box 42)
    - Clare Boothe Luce (Predate), Times-Herald, Apr 1946; 4 contacts and 4 negatives; additional contacts (Box 42)
    - Clare Boothe Luce's Birthday with Mrs. Farmington, Times-Herald, 10 Apr 1946; 7 contacts and 7 negatives; additional contacts (Box 42)
    - White House Spanish luncheon (Mrs. Allen, Mrs. Eisenhower, Mrs. Pearson, and Mrs. Patterson), Times-Herald, 19 Apr 1946; 8 contacts and 8 negatives; additional contacts (Box 42)
    - Noted editors at Washington Convention (O.Hobby, J.Daniels, and Blanche Smith), Times-Herald, 19 Apr 1946; 3 contacts and 8 negatives (Box 42)
    - Mexican Embassy (Ambassado de los Monteros with wife and Mrs. Patterson), Times-Herald, 23 Apr 1946; 1 contact and 1 negative (Box 42)
    - Korea's 1st Emissary Here: Miss Whang Kyung Koh, Times-Herald, 26 Apr 1946; 4 contacts and 4 negatives (Box 42)
    - Bendix VHF Radio (Pop Piper, Leona Koutz, Col. Bryan Evans), Times-Herald, 26 Apr 1946; 2 contacts and 2 negatives (Box 42)
    - Winifred Stillwell: General Omar Bradley's new aide, Times-Herald, 29 Apr 1946; 12 contacts and 12 negatives; additional contacts; See also Negatives and contacts: Newspaper negative 1939-1948: Winfred Stillwell (predate) (Box 42)
    - Edith Nourse Rogers at Walter Reed Hospital, Times-Herald, 01 May 1946; 4 contacts and 4 negatives; additional contacts (Box 42)
    - Vinsons and group leave for Kentucky Derby, Times-Herald, 02 May 1946; 3 contacts and 3 negatives; 3 additional negatives; additional contacts (Box 42)
    - Fertility clinic, Times-Herald, 02 May 1946; 3 contacts 3 negatives; additional contacts (Box 42)
    - Senator Brooks and fiancee, Mrs. Mary Peavey, Times-Herald, 04 May 1946; 9 contacts and 9 negatives (Box 42)
    - Matteo Mezzanotte and Claudia Stone Wed: Hollywood couple, Times-Herald, 04 May 1946; 3 contacts and 3 negatives; additional contacts; See also Negatives and contacts: Newspaper negatives 1939-1948: Mezzanotte and Stone (Box 42)
    - Warrenton VA Gold Cup Race: Mrs. Hunt; jockey; winner, Times-Herald, 05 May 1946; 6 negatives (Box 42)
    - British ambassador and Lady Halifax leaving embassy, Times-Herald, 14 May 1946; 3 contacts and 1 negative (Box 42)
    - Navajo Indians at the Senate; Chief Chee Dodge and Senator Hatch, Times-Herald, 14 May 1946; 2 contacts, no negatives (Box 42)
    - FBI (Flo Bratton, Deputy Sheriff), Times-Herald, 15 May 1946; 4 contacts and negatives; additional contacts (Box 42)
    - Reception for General Roxas, Phillipine President; with family, Times-Herald, 18 May 1946; 3 contacts and 3 negatives; additional negatives (Box 42)
    - Mme. Loudon, Netherlandish Embassy; with DC girls, Times-Herald, 21 May 1946; 3 contacts and 2 negatives (Box 42)
    - Lille Dache at LeBaron Farm Cattle Show, Warrenton, Va, Times-Herald, 21 May 1946; 3 contacts and 3 negatives; additional contacts (Box 42)
    - President Truman addresses Congress re: railroad strike, Times-Herald, 26 May 1946; 5 negatives (contact sheets and 35mm negatives in research folder) (Box 42)
    - Naval Academy and June Week Festival; Annapolis, MD, King, 05 Jun 1946; 27 contacts and negatives; additional contacts (Box 42)
    - Officials watching Louis Coun Fight on T.V. at Statler Hotel, 19 Jun 1946; 14 contacts and negatives (Box 42)
    - Bernard Barach, Times-Herald, 28 Jun 1946; 9 contacts and negatives; See also Projects and assignments: Newspaper features research files: Bernard Barach for more contacts. (Box 42)
    - Margaret Woodhouse is hired by mother/congresswoman, King, 26 Jun 1946; 2 contacts and 2 negatives; additional contacts (Box 42)
    - National Womens Press Club inauguration; Alice Rogers Hager receives Rigby Silver Bowl, 09 Jul 1946; No contacts, 3 negatives (Box 42)
    - Lion Statue and Capitol; British loan is passed. N.Y., 13 Jul 1946; 2 contacts and 2 negatives; additional negatives (Box 42)
    - Winfred Stillwell (predate), Boston, Times-Herald, 21 Jul 1946; contacts, no negatives; See also Negatives and contacts: Newspaper negatives 1939-1948: Winifred Stillwell: General Omar Bradley's new aide. (Box 42)
    - Rep. Helen Graham Douglas talks atomic energy, King, 27 Jul 1946; Contacts, no negatives (Box 42)
    - May's empty chair; amputees at Capitol Hill with Edith Nourse Rogers King, 29 Jul 1946; 1 negative; additional contacts (Box 42)
    - Clare Boothe Luce and amputees at Capitol Hill, Times-Herald, 01 Aug 1946; Contacts, no negatives (Box 42)
    - Peter Masefield and children at home; at airport, embassy, Times-Herald, 03 Aug 1946; 2 contacts and negatives; additional contacts (Box 42)
    - Saudi Arabian Minister and American wife with child, Times-Herald, 03 Aug 1946; No contacts, 3 negatives (Box 42)
    - William Benton, Asst. Secretary of State, and Czech girl, Times-Herald, 04 Aug 1946; 1 contact (Box 42)
    - GI vet and son studying at American University, 10 Aug 1946; 2 contacts and 2 negatives (Box 42)
    - Mezzanotte and Stone, Times-Herald, 14 Aug 1946; See also Negatives and contacts: Newspaper negatives 1939-1948: Matteo Mezzanotte and Claudia Stone Wed for negatives (Box 42)
    - Edith Debecker Sebald, 15 Aug 1946; 2 contacts and 2 negatives; additional contacts (Box 42)
    - James Maloney acting as Chief of Secret Service, 11 Sep 1946; 1 contact and 1 negative; additional contacts (Box 42)
    - Evie Robert portraits for Eleanor Patterson, 12 Sep 1946; contacts and negatives (Box 42)
    - President Truman at Walter Reed Hospital, 13 Sep 1946; No contacts, 2 negatives (Box 42)
    - Alice Rogers Hager and E. Johnston with Benton; UNESCO, 23 Sep 1946; 1 contact (Box 42)
    - "Bristol Freighter," Washington Airport; Peter Masefield, 23 Sep 1946; contacts, no negatives (Box 42)
    - John D. Hertz receives Medal of Merit from Secretary of Arms, 12 Oct 1947; contacts, no negatives (Box 42)
    - Guillermo DeBelt, Ambassador of Cuba, and family, Times-Herald, 02 Dec 1947; 2 contacts, no negatives (Box 42)
    - Gromyko with family, Times-Herald, 16 Aug 1946 (Box 42)
  - American Battle Monuments Commission, 1967
    - 2 containers of color transparencies, 25 slides (Box 43)
    - 1 binder of color transparencies showing cemeteries and war memorials (Box 43)
    - 3X4 and rollies (Box 43)
    - Ardennes, Belgium, 09 Oct 1967; negatives 3-28 (Box 43)
    - Britainnay, 20 Oct 1967; negatives 1-42 (Box 43)
    - Epinal, 23 Nov 1967-24 Nov 1967; negatives 1-40 (Box 43)
    - German Cemetary at LaCombe Calvados, 21 Oct 1967; negatives 1-11 (Box 43)
    - Henry Chapelle, 11 Oct 1940; negatives 1-40 (Box 43)
    - Netherlands, negatives, 1-4 (Box 43)
    - Normandy, negatives 1-61 (Box 43)
  - Brazil, 1941-1942
    - Rollies and 3X4 negatives (Box 43)
    - Jackie: photo story, See also Negatives and contacts: Brazil 1941-1942: Lagi factory, Rio A-B; Lagi plane factory (Box 43)
    - Jackie: Camocun (Box 43)
    - Amazon A, B and Santarem, Santarem A, B (Box 43)
    - Araxa (Box 43)
    - Belem Military Airport A-F; Old Pan-Air Airport and Strata Clipper Comet; Fairchild Amphibian and Hanger, street scenes, little paper and streetcar switchboys; zoo, biggest church; Interventor and Hager - palace and opera (Box 43)
    - Belem Market A-H (Box 43)
    - Belo Horizonte Farm - Florestal A-C (Box 43)
    - Gold Mine, Gold Mine C (Box 43)
    - New Airport D (Box 43)
    - New Military Airport (Box 43)
    - Belo Horizonte E-F (Box 43)
    - Athletic Club, gG (Box 43)
    - Camocun (Box 43)
    - Campinas A-B (Box 43)
    - Campanario A-C (Box 43)
    - Campos Dos Afonsos A-E; Rio (Box 43)
    - Campo Grande A-F; General ? with Mauro Pederneiras at military airport (Box 43)
    - Cloud, Infra-red Over Pantanol (Box 43)
    - Corumba A-B (Box 43)
    - The Christ, Rio A-C (Box 43)
    - Dr. Assis Figuerido, See also Negatives and contacts: Brazil 1941-1942: Fontes, Lourival and wife A-D (Box 43)
    - Florianapois: Naval Base, bear rug (Box 43)
    - Colonel Fontenelli and family (Box 43)
    - Fontes, Lourival and wife A-D; in study, on beach (Box 43)
    - Fontes, Senora alone (Box 43)
    - Fontes, Lourival and others (Box 43)
    - Forta Leza Jangadas Club with president of club A-B (Box 43)
    - Forta Leza Aero Club A-B (Box 43)
    - Gaucho Fazenda, A-F (Box 43)
    - Goias, A-C (Box 43)
    - Guayra A-C (Box 43)
    - Guaryra Falls (Box 43)
    - Gudin, Dr. A-D; with Jackie Martin; instruments he invented; gloves-rack; light-hands; tallow on lens-mask; close-ups of face and lamp; operation (Box 43)
    - Fargas, Senora with Grace Moore, Walt Dewey, Oswaldo Arauba (Box 43)
    - Hager, Alice Rogers (Box 43)
    - Iguassu A-C; Iguassu folks (Box 43)
    - Januario A-B (Box 43)
    - Lagi factory, Rio A-B; Lagi plane factory (Box 43)
    - Manaus A-D (Box 43)
    - Ouro Preto A-E (Box 43)
    - Petrolina A-C (Box 43)
    - Pocos de Caldos A-E; Pocos de Caldos (Box 43)
    - Porto Alegre Military Airport A-I; party for Alice Rogers Hager by Press Club (Box 43)
    - Rio, Military Airport, Santos Dumont; naval base, Appel Neto, all Brazilian-made plane and test pilot, A-C (Box 43)
    - Rio Aero Club, A-D (Box 43)
    - Rio street scenes A-B (Box 43)
    - Rio, from waterfront to naval air base (Box 43)
    - Rio, goodbye at airport (Box 43)
    - Sao Luiz A-B (Box 43)
    - Sao Paulo, Aero Club, A-G, Snakes (Box 43)
    - Sucury A-D (Box 43)
    - Therezopolis (Box 43)
    - Uberaba A-D (Box 43)
    - Una, crash (Box 43)
    - Union Station group (Box 43)
    - Urco Casino; dancers and flags (Box 43)
    - Vargas, Senora A-B; sewing group at Urca and J. Rice (Box 43)
    - Vargas, President and Alzira with Alice at Palace (Box 43)
    - Vargas, christening plane, Rio A-B; christening ship (Box 43)
    - Walt Disney and wife; Walt Disney, Sauiba School (Box 43)
    - Black and white negatives of color shots (Box 43)
    - "Brazilian Randolph" (Box 43)
  - Brazil: 35mm candids
    - Campos Dos Afontes-the Christ-Air-Santos Dumont Airport; dirigible hanger (Box 43)
    - Rio-operation of Dr. Gudin (Box 43)
    - Jungle hunt; Campanario; air shots, Guayra (Box 43)
    - Rio, Lagi factory; parade, sidewalks; Grace Moore recital (Box 43)
    - Infra-red; air; Rio to Belo Horizontes-Florestal; Corumba; Air (Box 43)
    - Infra-red; Porto Alegre; Vulter at Military Airport; commercial airport at Sao Paulo (Box 43)
    - Amazon; Manaus-Air; Rio Branca Joins Rio Nigre; clouds on River, Grupu (Box 43)
    - Up Amazon, Santarem (Box 43)
    - Belem air shots; wheels off Fairchild; mouth of Amazon; small airport before reaching Belem (Box 43)
    - Forteleza Airport; salt deposits and works between Camocun and Forteleza; dry rivers of Cearia (Box 43)
    - Going Up Sao Francisco (Box 43)
    - Sailboat at Belem; Curralino to Belem (Box 43)
  - Color transparencies, approximately 1000 total
    - Iguassu (I) (Box 43)
    - Uberaba (II) (Box 43)
    - Campo Dos Afonsos (III) (Box 43)
    - Naval Air Force Base (IV) (Box 43)
    - Petrolina V-A on Way to Camocun (V) (Box 43)
    - Sao Paulo (VI) (Box 43)
    - Up Amazon (VII) (Box 43)
    - Guayra (VIII) (Box 43)
    - Rio From Air; A-D (IX) (Box 43)
    - Pocos de Caldos (X) (Box 43)
    - Porto Alegro City (XI) (Box 43)
    - Ouro Preto (XII) (Box 43)
    - Market (XIII) (Box 43)
    - Airshot, Military Airport (XI) (Box 43)
    - Forteleza (XIV) (Box 43)
    - Mauros (XV) (Box 43)
    - Corumba (XVI) (Box 43)
    - Christ in Concrete (XVII) (Box 43)
    - Campo Grande (XVIII) (Box 43)
    - Theresopolis(XIX) (Box 43)
    - Senora Fontes (XX) (Box 43)
    - Santarem (XXI) (Box 43)
    - Sucury (XXII) (Box 43)
    - Goias (XXIII) (Box 43)
    - Araxa (XXIV) (Box 43)
    - Belo Horizonte; Belem Horizonte Farm (XV) (Box 43)
    - Gaucho Fozenda (XXVII) (Box 43)
    - Belem, Zoo, Airport (XXVIII) (Box 43)
    - Compenas (XXX) (Box 43)
    - Sao Luiz (XXXI) (Box 43)
    - Campanario (XXXII) (Box 43)
    - Santanol (XXXIII) (Box 43)
    - Januario (XXXIV) (Box 43)
    - Vargas Plane and Ship (XXXV) (Box 43)
    - Florianopolis (XXXVI) (Box 43)
    - Forteleza to Belem (XXXVII) (Box 43)
    - Miscellaneous (XXXVIII) (Box 43)
      Belem Military Airport; Floianopolis; Belo Horizonte, new military airport; Porto Alegre; Sao Luiz; Rio Aviation School (3); Sao Paulo, new plane; Flight - Fortaleza to Belem; Campanaria; Rio Air; Rio Airport take-offs; Rio AeroClub; Corovado (2); Naval Aviation, Rio; Campo Grande (5)
  - Marshall Plan film strips, 2 containers, 1 hard box, 1 2" canister
    - Dutch film strips no. 2 through no. 26, no. 29 through no. 32; 3 miscellaneous (Box 43)
    - C.I.S.L. filmstrips (9) hard box (Box 43)
    - Miscellaneous filmstrips and contacts in 2" canister (Box 43)
  - Europe
    - Paul Huf Studios, Amsterdam, 1960-1967; negatives 1-4 (Box 43)
    - "Cylindre" story, Paris - Lewis' shop, negatives 1-7 (Box 43)
    - "Cylindre", Paul Bart - Marche aux Pu, Paris, negatives 1-2 (Box 43)
    - "Cylindre," Village Swiss, Paris, negatives 1-16 (Box 43)
    - Grande Sablon, negatives 1-31 (rollie) (Box 43)
    - Marche Sablon, Oct 1967; rollie (Box 43)
    - Nompatelize, negatives 1-7 (Box 43)
    - Bruyeres, negative 1 (Box 43)
    - Paris, miscellaneous, negatives 1-7 (Box 43)
  - World War II War correspondent, 1944
    - 93rd Evacuation Hospital staging at Ft. Meade, MD (1-9) (Box 44)
    - Photos made aboard the Coast Guard ship "General Meigs" crossing from Norfolk to Naples (10), 09 Jul 1944 - 21 Jul 1944 (Box 44)
    - Aboard transport "General Meigs" (11-14B) (Box 44)
    - Early shots
      - Oran and Gela landing of 93rd (15) (Box 44)
      - Salerno and Anzio, 93rd (16) (Box 44)
      - 93rd at Anzio (17) (Box 44)
      - At Gaeta: French graves, Shaw; Cassino (18) (Box 44)
    - Benedictine Monastery at Cassino: Shots between Napoli-Cassino (19) (Box 44)
    - 93rd nurses in Naples (20) (Box 44)
    - 93rd staging area near Naples: General shots (21) (Box 44)
    - Nurses of 93rd in and around Naples: General Stayer (22) (Box 44)
    - 93rd nurses in Naples: Anne O'Hare McCormick, George Brandt (23) (Box 44)
    - 93rd nurses at Naples opera: Pompeii (24-26) (Box 44)
    - Stee scenes in Naples; Caserta (27) (Box 44)
    - Close-ups of Naples harbor D-2 (28) (Box 44)
    - Nurses at staging area; ready to leave D-2 (29) (Box 44)
    - D-2 nurses leaving area; boarding Marigold in harbor (30-31) (Box 44)
    - Nurses land at St. Topez; people at Salernes (32) (Box 44)
    - 93rd at Plan de la Tour; German 88 and shots on way to Rogenette (33-34) (Box 44)